Division of Invertebrate Zoology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Catalog Ledgers, 1864-Present; Series I
  - Gastropoda No's. 10833-13339. Complete ledger, contains duplicate No's 7100-10832., 1864-Present; 000959
    - gp11912. Individual page, 005430
    - gp11952. Individual page, 005431
    - gp11992. Individual page, 005432
    - gp12032. Individual page, 005433
    - gp12072. Individual page, 005434
    - gp12113. Individual page, 005435
    - gp12153. Individual page, 005436
    - gp12193. Individual page, 005437
    - gp12233. Individual page, 005438
    - gp12273. Individual page, 005439
    - gp12314. Individual page, 005440
    - gp12355. Individual page, 005441
    - gp12396. Individual page, 005442
    - gp12437. Individual page, 005443
    - gp12478. Individual page, 005444
    - gp12519. Individual page, 005445
    - gp12560. Individual page, 005446
    - gp12601. Individual page, 005447
    - gp12642. Individual page, 005448
    - gp12683. Individual page, 005449
    - gp12724. Individual page, 005450
    - gp12765. Individual page, 005451
    - gp12806. Individual page, 005452
    - gp12848. Individual page, 005453
    - gp12889. Individual page, 005454
    - gp12930. Individual page, 005455
    - gp12972. Individual page, 005456
    - gp13013. Individual page, 005457
    - gp13054. Individual page, 005458
    - gp13095. Individual page, 005459
    - gp13136. Individual page, 005460
    - gp13177. Individual page, 005461
    - gp13218. Individual page, 005462
    - gp13258. Individual page, 005463
    - gp13299. Individual page, 005464
  - Gastropoda No's. 13340-19475. Complete Ledger., 1864-Present; 000960
    - gp13340. Individual page, 005465
    - gp13384. Individual page, 005466
    - gp13428. Individual page, 005467
    - gp13470. Individual page, 005468
    - gp13510. Individual page, 005469
    - gp13550. Individual page, 005470
    - gp13590. Individual page, 005471
    - gp13630. Individual page, 005472
    - gp13670. Individual page, 005473
    - gp13710. Individual page, 005474
    - gp13750. Individual page, 005475
    - gp13790. Individual page, 005476
    - gp13830. Individual page, 005477
    - gp13870. Individual page, 005478
    - gp13910. Individual page, 005479
    - gp13950. Individual page, 005480
    - gp13990. Individual page, 005481
    - gp14030. Individual page, 005482
    - gp14070. Individual page, 005483
    - gp14110. Individual page, 005484
    - gp14150. Individual page, 005485
    - gp14190. Individual page, 005486
    - gp14230. Individual page, 005487
    - gp14270. Individual page, 005488
    - gp14310. Individual page, 005489
    - gp14350. Individual page, 005490
    - gp14390. Individual page, 005491
    - gp14430. Individual page, 005492
    - gp14470. Individual page, 005493
    - gp14510. Individual page, 005494
    - gp14550. Individual page, 005495
    - gp14590. Individual page, 005496
    - gp14630. Individual page, 005497
    - gp14670. Individual page, 005498
    - gp14710. Individual page, 005499
    - gp14750. Individual page, 005500
    - gp14790. Individual page, 005501
    - gp14830. Individual page, 005502
    - gp14870. Individual page, 005503
    - gp14910. Individual page, 005504
    - gp14950. Individual page, 005505
    - gp14990. Individual page, 005506
    - gp15030. Individual page, 005507
    - gp15070. Individual page, 005508
    - gp15110. Individual page, 005509
    - gp15150. Individual page, 005510
    - gp15190. Individual page, 005511
    - gp15230. Individual page, 005512
    - gp15270. Individual page, 005513
    - gp15310. Individual page, 005514
    - gp15350. Individual page, 005515
    - gp15390. Individual page, 005516
    - gp15430. Individual page, 005517
    - gp15470. Individual page, 005518
    - gp15510. Individual page, 005519
    - gp15550. Individual page, 005520
    - gp15590. Individual page, 005521
    - gp15630. Individual page, 005522
    - gp15670. Individual page, 005523
    - gp15710. Individual page, 005524
    - gp15750. Individual page, 005525
    - gp15790. Individual page, 005526
    - gp15830. Individual page, 005527
    - gp15870. Individual page, 005528
    - gp15910. Individual page, 005529
    - gp15950. Individual page, 005530
    - gp15990. Individual page, 005531
    - gp16030. Individual page, 005532
    - gp16070. Individual page, 005533
    - gp16110. Individual page, 005534
    - gp16150. Individual page, 005535
    - gp16190. Individual page, 005536
    - gp16230. Individual page, 005537
    - gp16270. Individual page, 005538
    - gp16310. Individual page, 005539
    - gp16350. Individual page, 005540
    - gp16390. Individual page, 005541
    - gp16430. Individual page, 005542
    - gp16470. Individual page, 005543
    - gp16510. Individual page, 005544
    - gp16550. Individual page, 005545
    - gp16590. Individual page, 005546
    - gp16630. Individual page, 005547
    - gp16670. Individual page, 005548
    - gp16710. Individual page, 005549
    - gp16750. Individual page, 005550
    - gp16790. Individual page, 005551
    - gp16830. Individual page, 005552
    - gp16870. Individual page, 005553
    - gp16910. Individual page, 005554
    - gp16950. Individual page, 005555
    - gp16990. Individual page, 005556
    - gp17030. Individual page, 005557
    - gp17070. Individual page, 005558
    - gp17110. Individual page, 005559
    - gp17150. Individual page, 005560
    - gp17190. Individual page, 005561
    - gp17230. Individual page, 005562
    - gp17270. Individual page, 005563
    - gp17310. Individual page, 005564
    - gp17350. Individual page, 005565
    - gp17390. Individual page, 005566
    - gp17430. Individual page, 005567
    - gp17470. Individual page, 005568
    - gp17510. Individual page, 005569
    - gp17550. Individual page, 005570
    - gp17590. Individual page, 005571
    - gp17630. Individual page, 005572
    - gp17670. Individual page, 005573
    - gp17710. Individual page, 005574
    - gp17751. Individual page, 005575
    - gp17791. Individual page, 005576
    - gp17831. Individual page, 005577
    - gp17871. Individual page, 005578
    - gp17911. Individual page, 005579
    - gp17951. Individual page, 005580
    - gp17991. Individual page, 005581
    - gp18031. Individual page, 005582
    - gp18071. Individual page, 005583
    - gp18111. Individual page, 005584
    - gp18151. Individual page, 005585
    - gp18191. Individual page, 005586
    - gp18231. Individual page, 005587
    - gp18271. Individual page, 005588
    - gp18311. Individual page, 005589
    - gp18351. Individual page, 005590
    - gp18391. Individual page, 005591
    - gp18431. Individual page, 005592
    - gp18471. Individual page, 005593
    - gp18511. Individual page, 005594
    - gp18551. Individual page, 005595
    - gp18591. Individual page, 005596
    - gp18631. Individual page, 005597
    - gp18671. Individual page, 005598
    - gp18711. Individual page, 005599
    - gp18751. Individual page, 005600
    - gp18791. Individual page, 005601
    - gp18831. Individual page, 005602
    - gp18871. Individual page, 005603
    - gp18911. Individual page, 005604
    - gp18951. Individual page, 005605
    - gp18991. Individual page, 005606
    - gp19011. Individual page, 005607
    - gp19031. Individual page, 005608
    - gp19051. Individual page, 005609
    - gp19071. Individual page, 005610
    - gp19091. Individual page, 005611
    - gp19111. Individual page, 005612
    - gp19131. Individual page, 005613
    - gp19151. Individual page, 005614
    - gp19171. Individual page, 005615
    - gp19191. Individual page, 005616
    - gp19211. Individual page, 005617
    - gp19231. Individual page, 005618
    - gp19251. Individual page, 005619
    - gp19271. Individual page, 005620
    - gp19291. Individual page, 005621
    - gp19311. Individual page, 005622
    - gp19331. Individual page, 005623
    - gp19351. Individual page, 005624
    - gp19371. Individual page, 005625
    - gp19391. Individual page, 005626
    - gp19411. Individual page, 005627
    - gp19431. Individual page, 005628
    - gp19451. Individual page, 005629
    - gp19471. Individual page, 005630
  - Gastropoda No's. 5076-10832. Complete Ledger., 1864-Present; 000958
    - gp05076. Individual page, 005172
    - gp05101. Individual page, 005173
    - gp05126. Individual page, 005174
    - gp05151. Individual page, 005175
    - gp05176. Individual page, 005176
    - gp05201. Individual page, 005177
    - gp05226. Individual page, 005178
    - gp05251. Individual page, 005179
    - gp05276. Individual page, 005180
    - gp05301. Individual page, 005181
    - gp05326. Individual page, 005182
    - gp05351. Individual page, 005183
    - gp05376. Individual page, 005184
    - gp05401. Individual page, 005185
    - gp05426. Individual page, 005186
    - gp05451. Individual page, 005187
    - gp05476. Individual page, 005188
    - gp05501. Individual page, 005189
    - gp05526. Individual page, 005190
    - gp05551. Individual page, 005191
    - gp05576. Individual page, 005192
    - gp05601. Individual page, 005193
    - gp05626. Individual page, 005194
    - gp05651. Individual page, 005195
    - gp05676. Individual page, 005196
    - gp05701. Individual page, 005197
    - gp05726. Individual page, 005198
    - gp05751. Individual page, 005199
    - gp05776. Individual page, 005200
    - gp05801. Individual page, 005201
    - gp05826. Individual page, 005202
    - gp05851. Individual page, 005203
    - gp05876. Individual page, 005204
    - gp05901. Individual page, 005205
    - gp05926. Individual page, 005206
    - gp05951. Individual page, 005207
    - gp05976. Individual page, 005208
    - gp06001. Individual page, 005209
    - gp06026. Individual page, 005210
    - gp06051. Individual page, 005211
    - gp06076. Individual page, 005212
    - gp06101. Individual page, 005213
    - gp06126. Individual page, 005214
    - gp06151. Individual page, 005215
    - gp06176. Individual page, 005216
    - gp06201. Individual page, 005217
    - gp06226. Individual page, 005218
    - gp06251. Individual page, 005219
    - gp06276. Individual page, 005220
    - gp06301. Individual page, 005221
    - gp06326. Individual page, 005222
    - gp06351. Individual page, 005223
    - gp06376. Individual page, 005224
    - gp06401. Individual page, 005225
    - gp06426. Individual page, 005226
    - gp06451. Individual page, 005227
    - gp06476. Individual page, 005228
    - gp06501. Individual page, 005229
    - gp06526. Individual page, 005230
    - gp06551. Individual page, 005231
    - gp06576. Individual page, 005232
    - gp06601. Individual page, 005233
    - gp06626. Individual page, 005234
    - gp06651. Individual page, 005235
    - gp06676. Individual page, 005236
    - gp06701. Individual page, 005237
    - gp06726. Individual page, 005238
    - gp06751. Individual page, 005239
    - gp06776. Individual page, 005240
    - gp06801. Individual page, 005241
    - gp06826. Individual page, 005242
    - gp06851. Individual page, 005243
    - gp06876. Individual page, 005244
    - gp06901. Individual page, 005245
    - gp06926. Individual page, 005246
    - gp06951. Individual page, 005247
    - gp06976. Individual page, 005248
    - gp07001. Individual page, 005249
    - gp07026. Individual page, 005250
    - gp07051. Individual page, 005251
    - gp07076. Individual page, 005252
    - gp07101. Individual page, 005253
    - gp07126. Individual page, 005254
    - gp07151. Individual page, 005255
    - gp07176. Individual page, 005256
    - gp07201. Individual page, 005257
    - gp07226. Individual page, 005258
    - gp07251. Individual page, 005259
    - gp07276. Individual page, 005260
    - gp07301. Individual page, 005261
    - gp07326. Individual page, 005262
    - gp07351. Individual page, 005263
    - gp07376. Individual page, 005264
    - gp07401. Individual page, 005265
    - gp07426. Individual page, 005266
    - gp07451. Individual page, 005267
    - gp07476. Individual page, 005268
    - gp07501. Individual page, 005269
    - gp07526. Individual page, 005270
    - gp07551. Individual page, 005271
    - gp07576. Individual page, 005272
    - gp07601. Individual page, 005273
    - gp07626. Individual page, 005274
    - gp07651. Individual page, 005275
    - gp07676. Individual page, 005276
    - gp07701. Individual page, 005277
    - gp07726. Individual page, 005278
    - gp07751. Individual page, 005279
    - gp07776. Individual page, 005280
    - gp07801. Individual page, 005281
    - gp07826. Individual page, 005282
    - gp07851. Individual page, 005283
    - gp07876. Individual page, 005284
    - gp07901. Individual page, 005285
    - gp07926. Individual page, 005286
    - gp07951. Individual page, 005287
    - gp07976. Individual page, 005288
    - gp08001. Individual page, 005289
    - gp08026. Individual page, 005290
    - gp08051. Individual page, 005291
    - gp08076. Individual page, 005292
    - gp08101. Individual page, 005293
    - gp08126. Individual page, 005294
    - gp08151. Individual page, 005295
    - gp08176. Individual page, 005296
    - gp08201. Individual page, 005297
    - gp08226. Individual page, 005298
    - gp08251. Individual page, 005299
    - gp08276. Individual page, 005300
    - gp08301. Individual page, 005301
    - gp08326. Individual page, 005302
    - gp08351. Individual page, 005303
    - gp08376. Individual page, 005304
    - gp08401. Individual page, 005305
    - gp08426. Individual page, 005306
    - gp08451. Individual page, 005307
    - gp08476. Individual page, 005308
    - gp08501. Individual page, 005309
    - gp08526. Individual page, 005310
    - gp08551. Individual page, 005311
    - gp08576. Individual page, 005312
    - gp08601. Individual page, 005313
    - gp08626. Individual page, 005314
    - gp08651. Individual page, 005315
    - gp08676. Individual page, 005316
    - gp08701. Individual page, 005317
    - gp08726. Individual page, 005318
    - gp08751. Individual page, 005319
    - gp08776. Individual page, 005320
    - gp08801. Individual page, 005321
    - gp08826. Individual page, 005322
    - gp08851. Individual page, 005323
    - gp08876. Individual page, 005324
    - gp08901. Individual page, 005325
    - gp08926. Individual page, 005326
    - gp08951. Individual page, 005327
    - gp08976. Individual page, 005328
    - gp09001. Individual page, 005329
    - gp09026. Individual page, 005330
    - gp09051. Individual page, 005331
    - gp09076. Individual page, 005332
    - gp09101. Individual page, 005333
    - gp09126. Individual page, 005334
    - gp09151. Individual page, 005335
    - gp09176. Individual page, 005336
    - gp09201. Individual page, 005337
    - gp09226. Individual page, 005338
    - gp09251. Individual page, 005339
    - gp09276. Individual page, 005340
    - gp09301. Individual page, 005341
    - gp09326. Individual page, 005342
    - gp09351. Individual page, 005343
    - gp09376. Individual page, 005344
    - gp09401. Individual page, 005345
    - gp09426. Individual page, 005346
    - gp09451. Individual page, 005347
    - gp09476. Individual page, 005348
    - gp09501. Individual page, 005349
    - gp09526. Individual page, 005350
    - gp09551. Individual page, 005351
    - gp09576. Individual page, 005352
    - gp09601. Individual page, 005353
    - gp09626. Individual page, 005354
    - gp09651. Individual page, 005355
    - gp09676. Individual page, 005356
    - gp09701. Individual page, 005357
    - gp09726. Individual page, 005358
    - gp09751. Individual page, 005359
    - gp09776. Individual page, 005360
    - gp09801. Individual page, 005361
    - gp09826. Individual page, 005362
    - gp09851. Individual page, 005363
    - gp09876. Individual page, 005364
    - gp09901. Individual page, 005365
    - gp09926. Individual page, 005366
    - gp09951. Individual page, 005367
    - gp09976. Individual page, 005368
    - gp10001. Individual page, 005369
    - gp10026. Individual page, 005370
    - gp10051. Individual page, 005371
    - gp10076. Individual page, 005372
    - gp10101. Individual page, 005373
    - gp10126. Individual page, 005374
    - gp10151. Individual page, 005375
    - gp10176. Individual page, 005376
    - gp10201. Individual page, 005377
    - gp10226. Individual page, 005378
    - gp10251. Individual page, 005379
    - gp10276. Individual page, 005380
    - gp10301. Individual page, 005381
    - gp10326. Individual page, 005382
    - gp10351. Individual page, 005383
    - gp10376. Individual page, 005384
    - gp10401. Individual page, 005385
    - gp10426. Individual page, 005386
    - gp10451. Individual page, 005387
    - gp10476. Individual page, 005388
    - gp10501. Individual page, 005389
    - gp10526. Individual page, 005390
    - gp10551. Individual page, 005391
    - gp10576. Individual page, 005392
    - gp10601. Individual page, 005393
    - gp10626. Individual page, 005394
    - gp10651. Individual page, 005395
    - gp10676. Individual page, 005396
    - gp10701. Individual page, 005397
    - gp10726. Individual page, 005398
    - gp10751. Individual page, 005399
    - gp10776. Individual page, 005400
    - gp10801. Individual page, 005401
    - gp10826. Individual page, 005402
  - Mollusca. Mollusca Ledgers., 1864-Present; 000952
    - Mollusca. Mollusca. United States Fisheries Commission Specimens. USNM numbers., 1864-Present; 000953
    - Mollusca. Bivalvia. No's. 3000-4846. Transferred to new volume., 1864-Present; 000961
    - Mollusca. Catalogue of Acephala. Original Bivalvia ledger. YPM No's. 1-3085., 1866; 001089
    - Mollusca. Gatropoda. Volume I. Original Gastropoda ledger. YPM No's. 1-5075., 1866; 001090
    - Mollusca. Gatropoda. Volume II. Original Gastropoda ledger. YPM No's. 5076-7100., 1866; 001091
    - Mollusca. Several Mollusca catalogs. Labeled "Old Catalogues, etc." Some are lists of Mollusca in the "Yale College Cabinet", pre 1864., 001701
  - Nemertea No's. 1-226., 1864-Present; 004069
    - nm001. Individual page, 004190
    - nm026. Individual page, 004191
    - nm051. Individual page, 004192
    - nm076. Individual page, 004193
    - nm101. Individual page, 004194
    - nm126. Individual page, 004195
    - nm151. Individual page, 004196
    - nm176. Individual page, 004197
    - nm201. Individual page, 004198
    - nm226. Individual page, 004199
  - Porifera No's. 1-3975. Complete Ledger., 1864-Present; 000964
    - pr00001. Individual page, 004230
    - pr00026. Individual page, 004231
    - pr00051. Individual page, 004232
    - pr00076. Individual page, 004233
    - pr00101. Individual page, 004234
    - pr00126. Individual page, 004235
    - pr00151. Individual page, 004236
    - pr00176. Individual page, 004237
    - pr00201. Individual page, 004238
    - pr00226. Individual page, 004239
    - pr00251. Individual page, 004240
    - pr00276. Individual page, 004241
    - pr00301. Individual page, 004242
    - pr00326. Individual page, 004243
    - pr00351. Individual page, 004244
    - pr00376. Individual page, 004245
    - pr00401. Individual page, 004246
    - pr00426. Individual page, 004247
    - pr00451. Individual page, 004248
    - pr00476. Individual page, 004249
    - pr00501. Individual page, 004250
    - pr00526. Individual page, 004251
    - pr00551. Individual page, 004252
    - pr00576. Individual page, 004253
    - pr00601. Individual page, 004254
    - pr00626. Individual page, 004255
    - pr00651. Individual page, 004256
    - pr00676. Individual page, 004257
    - pr00701. Individual page, 004258
    - pr00726. Individual page, 004259
    - pr00751. Individual page, 004260
    - pr00776. Individual page, 004261
    - pr00801. Individual page, 004262
    - pr00826. Individual page, 004263
    - pr00851. Individual page, 004264
    - pr00876. Individual page, 004265
    - pr00901. Individual page, 004266
    - pr00926. Individual page, 004267
    - pr00951. Individual page, 004268
    - pr00976. Individual page, 004269
    - pr01001. Individual page, 004270
    - pr01026. Individual page, 004271
    - pr01051. Individual page, 004272
    - pr01076. Individual page, 004273
    - pr01101. Individual page, 004274
    - pr01126. Individual page, 004275
    - pr01151. Individual page, 004276
    - pr01176. Individual page, 004277
    - pr01201. Individual page, 004278
    - pr01226. Individual page, 004279
    - pr01251. Individual page, 004280
    - pr01276. Individual page, 004281
    - pr01301. Individual page, 004282
    - pr01326. Individual page, 004283
    - pr01351. Individual page, 004284
    - pr01376. Individual page, 004285
    - pr01401. Individual page, 004286
    - pr01426. Individual page, 004287
    - pr01451. Individual page, 004288
    - pr01476. Individual page, 004289
    - pr01501. Individual page, 004290
    - pr01526. Individual page, 004291
    - pr01551. Individual page, 004292
    - pr01576. Individual page, 004293
    - pr01601. Individual page, 004294
    - pr01626. Individual page, 004295
    - pr01651. Individual page, 004296
    - pr01676. Individual page, 004297
    - pr01701. Individual page, 004298
    - pr01726. Individual page, 004299
    - pr01751. Individual page, 004300
    - pr01776. Individual page, 004301
    - pr01801. Individual page, 004302
    - pr01826. Individual page, 004303
    - pr01851. Individual page, 004304
    - pr01876. Individual page, 004305
    - pr01901. Individual page, 004306
    - pr01926. Individual page, 004307
    - pr01951. Individual page, 004308
    - pr01976. Individual page, 004309
    - pr02001. Individual page, 004310
    - pr02026. Individual page, 004311
    - pr02051. Individual page, 004312
    - pr02076. Individual page, 004313
    - pr02101. Individual page, 004314
    - pr02126. Individual page, 004315
    - pr02151. Individual page, 004316
    - pr02176. Individual page, 004317
    - pr02201. Individual page, 004318
    - pr02226. Individual page, 004319
    - pr02251. Individual page, 004320
    - pr02276. Individual page, 004321
    - pr02301. Individual page, 004322
    - pr02326. Individual page, 004323
    - pr02351. Individual page, 004324
    - pr02376. Individual page, 004325
    - pr02401. Individual page, 004326
    - pr02426. Individual page, 004327
    - pr02451. Individual page, 004328
    - pr02476. Individual page, 004329
    - pr02501. Individual page, 004330
    - pr02526. Individual page, 004331
    - pr02551. Individual page, 004332
    - pr02576. Individual page, 004333
    - pr02601. Individual page, 004334
    - pr02626. Individual page, 004335
    - pr02651. Individual page, 004336
    - pr02676. Individual page, 004337
    - pr02701. Individual page, 004338
    - pr02726. Individual page, 004339
    - pr02751. Individual page, 004340
    - pr02776. Individual page, 004341
    - pr02801. Individual page, 004342
    - pr02826. Individual page, 004343
    - pr02851. Individual page, 004344
    - pr02876. Individual page, 004345
    - pr02901. Individual page, 004346
    - pr02926. Individual page, 004347
    - pr02951. Individual page, 004348
    - pr02976. Individual page, 004349
    - pr03001. Individual page, 004350
    - pr03026. Individual page, 004351
    - pr03051. Individual page, 004352
    - pr03076. Individual page, 004353
    - pr03101. Individual page, 004354
    - pr03126. Individual page, 004355
    - pr03151. Individual page, 004356
    - pr03176. Individual page, 004357
    - pr03201. Individual page, 004358
    - pr03226. Individual page, 004359
    - pr03251. Individual page, 004360
    - pr03276. Individual page, 004361
    - pr03301. Individual page, 004362
    - pr03326. Individual page, 004363
    - pr03351. Individual page, 004364
    - pr03376. Individual page, 004365
    - pr03401. Individual page, 004366
    - pr03426. Individual page, 004367
    - pr03451. Individual page, 004368
    - pr03476. Individual page, 004369
    - pr03501. Individual page, 004370
    - pr03526. Individual page, 004371
    - pr03551. Individual page, 004372